(Howard:)Good night.
(Howard:)I love both my girls.
(Bernadette:)We love you, too.
(Penny:)I can't believe
you fit in the crib.
(Bernadette:)I could take a bath
in the sink.
(Bernadette:)I don't, but I can.
(Raj:)So how were your holidays?
(Stuart:)Oh, thank you for asking.
(Stuart:)Uh, I, uh,
went to visit my grandmother.
(Stuart:)She's in Bakersfield.
(Stuart:)Uh, usually my brother
and sister go...
Oh, come on!
(Amy:)That was fun, thank you.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, thanks.
(Penny:)Our pleasure.
See you guys at work.
(Raj:)Be there bright and early.
(Howard:)Not me, paternity leave.
Oh!
(Sheldon:)A small human
(Sheldon:)wreaks havoc
on his wife's genitals
(Sheldon:)and he gets time off.
With pay, sucka!
(Howard:)Forgot the baby,
still new to this.